Shop Now

20% Off Framing, Canvas & Mount on Orders $99+ Ends in..

1DAYS19HRS15MINS

20% Off Framing, Canvas & Mount on Orders $99+ Ends in..

1DAYS19HRS15MINS

Shop Now

Cancel

My Account

Cancel

Help
----

####   

#### Customer Service

#### My Account

#### Our Products

#### Corporate Policies

Privacy Notice
==============

_Last Updated: Dec 22, 2022._

Updates include:

* Updated California Privacy Rights section
* Addition of Virginia Privacy Rights
* Revised disclosures about the categories of personal information we may collect
* Revised disclosures about how we collect information
* Revised disclosures about how we use your information
* Clarification about how long we retain your personal information and how we protect it
* Clarification about how we link to other websites

We have implemented this Privacy Notice to inform you of the personal information that we collect from you when you visit this website and other websites where this notice is posted, use our mobile app online services or otherwise interact with us offline, what we do with your personal information and how you can exercise your privacy rights.

We may collect or receive the following categories of personal information. Not all categories may be collected or received about every individual:

* Identifiers: Personal identifiers, such as name, telephone number, physical address, email address, government-issued identifiers (e.g., national identification numbers, driver's license numbers), and signatures
* Device Information and Online Activity: Device and online identifiers, account login information, keystroke patterns indicative of human or bot website/app usage, mobile and web network activity and related information (such as Mac address, IP address, cookie IDs, browser activity, and other information associated with your browsing history), and social media information
* Commercial Information: Purchase and transaction history information (such as products or services you have purchased, rented, or returned), health and safety-related information, product testimonials, travel and vacation information, and competition entries
* Communications: Communication details (such as the content of emails, text messages, or other communications), call logs, and calendar information where we are a party to the exchange
* Demographic Information: Demographic information, such as age (including information about children under the age of 13 with respect to certain purchases and services (e.g., tobacco purchases), gender, citizenship, ethnicity, date of birth, family or marital status, household income, education, professional and employment information, family health, number of children, number of cars owned, and software or virtual assets owned
* Financial Information: Financial information, such as credit or debit card numbers, financial account numbers, and claims information
* Biometric Information: Biometric information, such as voice prints, imagery of the iris or retina, face geometry, and palm prints or fingerprints
* Geolocation: Location information, such as geolocation information
* Sensory Information: Audio, visual information, and other sensory information such as photographs and audio and video recordings
* Background Information: Background and criminal information, such as background checks and criminal convictions
* Inferences: Individual preferences and characteristics, such as inferences related to shopping patterns and behaviors, intelligence, and aptitudes

###   

How Do We Collect Information
-----------------------------

We collect information from you in a variety of ways. It may be:

* Provided directly by you or a member of your household
* Collected from a device associated with you or your household
* Collected from another company within our family of companies
* Collected from an external third-party source
* Collected from another solution or asset
* Collected from other sources, when it is appropriate, to help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our services, increase the appeal and relevance of advertising, and to prevent or detect fraud

Our goal is to limit the information we collect to the information needed to support our business.

_Information provided directly by you or a member of your household_

When you interact with our online services, we may ask you to provide personal information voluntarily: for example, we ask you to provide your name, contact details and payment details in order to purchase a printed product from us or to set up an online account, or your email address to sign up to receive a newsletter and/or to submit inquiries to us. We may ask for similar information when you contact us offline, for example for customer service.

The personal information that you are asked to provide, and the reasons why you are asked to provide it, will be made clear to you at the point we ask you to provide your personal information.

_Information collected from a device associated with you or your household_

When you use our online services, we may collect certain information automatically from your device. Specifically, the information we collect automatically may include information like your IP address, browser type, the URL of the previous website you visited, your ISP, operating system and other technical information. We may also collect information about how your device has interacted with our online services, including the pages accessed and links clicked.

Collecting this information enables us to better diagnose problems with our server and to administer our online services, as well as understand the visitors who use our online services, where they come from, and what content is of interest to them. This information aids us in merchandising and in developing the design, layout and functionality of the online services. Some of this information may be collected using cookies and similar tracking technology, as explained further on our '[Cookies and similar tracking technology](https://www.art.com/help/cookies)' page.

_Information We Collect from Another Company within Our Family of Companies_

We may collect your personal information from another organization within our corporate family of companies, such as Trends International.

_Information Collected from External Third-Party Sources_

We receive personal information about you from other sources to help us correct or supplement our records, improve the quality or personalization of our service to you, prevent or detect fraud, and for other business purposes. We also receive information, such as device information and browsing information, from third parties for marketing purposes, for example, to provide you with personalized ads on Art.com and third-party websites and mobile services.

###   

What we do with your personal information
-----------------------------------------

We may use the information we collect through our online services for a number of purposes, including to:

* Performing services, including maintaining or servicing accounts, providing customer service, processing or fulfilling orders and transactions, verifying customer information, processing payments, providing financing, providing analytics services, providing storage, or providing similar services
* Providing advertising and marketing services, including targeted advertising
* To conduct auditing and monitoring of transactions and engagement, including auditing related to counting ad impressions to unique visitors, verifying positioning and quality of ad impressions, and auditing compliance
* Short-term, transient use, such as non-personalized advertising shown as part of your current interaction with us
* Helping to ensure security and integrity and prevent fraud
* Undertaking activities to verify or maintain the quality or safety of our services or devices and to improve, upgrade, or enhance them
* Debugging to identify and repair errors
* To conduct business analysis, such as analytics, projections, identifying areas for operational improvement
* To conduct research and development, including undertaking internal research for technological development and demonstration
* To fulfill our legal functions or obligations

We may use sensitive personal information for each of the purposes described above and to make inferences about customers, which we may use to promote certain products or services.

To the extent we process de-identified information, we will maintain and use the information in de-identified form and will not attempt to reidentify the information unless permitted by applicable law.

###   

Who we disclose information to
------------------------------

We are careful to disclose your personal information in ways that respect your privacy and only as described in this Notice. We view you as a valued customer, not a product, and we do not sell or rent your personal information to others for money.

We may share and disclose your personal information to other third parties in the following circumstances:

* Within the Trends International. family of companies. When we do, the information will be used in ways that are consistent with this Notice.
* To vendors and other third-party service providers who require access to your personal information to assist in the provision of the online services, our products and services, and other business-related functions. For example, we partner with one or more credit card processing companies to assist us in processing your payment. We partner with third parties that offer credit checks services that review credit worthiness of certain users to manage our risk and help us to avoid sending out orders to users that cannot afford to pay. We may also work with third party service providers to assist us providing targeted email campaigns, assemble and prepare personalized offers and/or make particular product or purchase recommendations. However, those companies do not retain, disclose, store, or use personal information for any secondary purposes.
* We may also disclose your personal information to third parties: (a) where required by law or regulatory requirement, court order or other judicial authorization, (b) in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including for the purposes of meeting national security and law enforcement requirements; (c) in connection with the sale, transfer, merger, bankruptcy, restructuring or other reorganization of a business; (d) to protect or defend our rights, interests or property, or that of third parties; (e) to investigate any wrongdoing in connection with the online services or our services; (f) to protect the vital interests of an individual.
* To an actual or potential buyer (and its agents and advisers) in connection with any actual or proposed purchase, merger or acquisition of any part of our business, provided that we inform the buyer it must use your personal information only for the purposes disclosed in this Privacy Notice;
* Deidentified & Aggregated Personal Information: We continually strive to make customer shopping experiences more relevant and with less friction and may offer related services and insights to our suppliers and others. As a result, we may disclose to others insights that combine information from many customers in ways that do not directly identify you. For example, we may combine your shopping history with that of other customers to deliver generalized insights to our suppliers. These insights do not identify individual customers. This information helps our suppliers provide products and services relevant to our customers. We may receive payment for these insights.To deliver information about products and services that may be of interest to you, we may disclose information with other companies, such as publishers, advertisers and measurement analytics providers. For example, we may disclose device-related data (such as device identifier, type of device, IP address, cookies and other information associated with your browsing and app usage) and individual preferences and characteristics (such as insights and inferences related to shopping patterns and behaviors). This information does not identify you directly, but is necessary to personalize the advertisements you receive. We do not receive payment for this information. For more information about your choices related to advertising activities see "[Cookies and Similar Tracking Technology](https://www.art.com/help/cookies)".
* To any other person with your consent.

_Categories of Personal Information We Disclose to Each Type of Third Party:_

We may disclose your personal information with certain categories of third parties, as described below.

Types of Third Parties to Which the Personal Information Was Disclosed for a Business PurposeCategories of Personal Information Disclosed for a Business PurposeThose we are legally required to disclose toAudio, visual, and other sensory information

Characteristics of protected classifications under state or federal law

Demographic information

Device and online identifiers and related information

Employment information

Financial information

Individual preferences and characteristics

Internet, application, and network activity

Location information

Personal identifiers

Purchase history informationService providers that receive data in order to provide services to us (e.g. technology providers, cloud storage providers, etc.)Audio, visual, and other sensory information

Device and online identifiers and related information

Employment information

Financial information

Internet, application, and network activity

Location information

Personal identifiers

Purchase history informationThird parties with whom individuals direct us to disclose their personal informationDevice and online identifiers and related information

Employment information

Internet, application, and network activity

Location information

Personal identifiers

Purchase history information

###   

Cookies and similar tracking technology
---------------------------------------

Like other e-commerce web sites, we use 'cookies' and other technologies to collect information and enhance features and functionality. Cookies are bits of information that are stored on your computer by your web browser. They do allow us to do things like keep items in your shopping cart between visits or during the same visit or provide you with a more personalized user experience.

Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. The 'Help' portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to be notified when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. You can also disable or delete similar data used by browser add-ons, such as Flash cookies, by changing the add-ons settings or visiting the website of its manufacturer.

However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some of features and services, we recommend that you leave them turned on. For instance, if you block our cookies, you will not be able to add items to your cart, proceed to checkout, or use any services that require you to sign in. If you have not changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies.

We use third-party service providers to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet and sometimes on our online services. They may collect information about your use of our online services, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services.

This information is collected by a pixel tag, which is industry standard technology used by most major web sites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by our third party service provider, please visit our "[About our Ads](https://www.art.com/help/ads)" page. You can also read more about online marketing practices and the technologies that support them by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's website by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

To find out more about the cookies that we serve and how to manage your cookie opt-outs, click [here](https://www.art.com/help/cookies).

We use third parties to improve our ability to identify visitors to our website. As part of this service, we may make available identifiers to these third parties including our visitors' IP addresses, cookies, and hashed versions of email addresses captured from your visit. We, and third parties, use this data to obtain more information about our visitors and reach out to them through other channels, such as email and/or direct mail. You have the right to opt-out of this activity. To opt-out, please follow the instructions in [Your data protection rights & choices](https://www.art.com/help/privacy-policy)

###   

International data transfers
----------------------------

Your personal information may be stored and processed by us in any country where we or our service providers have facilities, and your personal information may therefore be transferred to countries outside of your country of residence, including the U.S., which may have different data protection rules to those of your country. Specifically, we may transfer your personal and non-personal information to Art.com for processing and storage in the U.S. By interacting with our online services, you consent to such transfers.

###   

How we protect your information
-------------------------------

We use reasonable information security measures, including physical, administrative, and technical safeguards.

###   

Your data protection rights & choices
-------------------------------------

You have the following rights:

* If you wish to access, correct, update or request deletion of your personal information, you can do so at any time by contacting us using the contact details provided under 'How to contact us' heading [below](https://www.art.com/help/privacy-policy). You can correct many of the details in your account by logging in to your account.
* You have the right to opt-out of marketing communications we send you at any time. You can exercise this right by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link in the marketing e-mails we send you. Alternatively, please contact us at [privacy@art.com](mailto:privacy@art.com). Please include your complete name, e-mail address and mailing address. Note that it may take up to three business days to remove you from our marketing lists and after this point you may still receive customer service related communications from us.

We respond to all requests we receive from individuals wishing to exercise their data protection rights in accordance with applicable data protection laws. For additional information regarding your choices, please visit our [About or Ads](https://www.art.com/help/ads) page.

###   

Your State Privacy Rights
-------------------------

_Virginia Consumer Data Protection Act:_

Virginia residents can exercise the following rights by going to the footer of our website or settings section of our app and selecting the "Request My Personal Information" link:

1. Request to Access My Personal Information
2. Delete My Personal Information
3. Correct My Personal Information

Virginia residents can exercise the following rights by going to the footer of our website or the settings section of our app and selecting the "My Privacy Choices" link:

1. Opt Out of the Processing of My Personal Information for Purposes of Targeted Advertising

If we decline to take action on one of your rights as a Virginia resident, you can submit an appeal by going to our privacy request page.

_California Consumer Privacy Act:_

Note: This Notice uses certain terms that have the meaning given to them in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act of 2020) and its implementing regulations.

###   

Sale and Sharing of Personal Information
----------------------------------------

We may sell or share personal information with third parties for various purposes including cross-context behavioral advertising or sharing among Trends International-affiliated entities. These kinds of disclosures may be deemed selling or sharing personal information under California law and you have the right to opt out of these disclosures. We may sell or share for cross-context behavioral advertising purposes (and may have sold or shared during the 12-month period prior to the Last Updated date of this Notice) the following categories of personal information to the following categories of third parties:

Categories of Personal Information Sold or SharedCategories of Third-Party ReceipientIdentifiersService providers (such as advertising networks, marketplace sellers, analytics providers, etc.)Device Information and Online ActivityBusiness partners that receive data for their own independent use and not to provide services to a Trends International entityDemographic InformationBusiness partners that receive data for their own independent use and not to provide services to a Trends International entity; Service providers that receive data to provide services to a Trends International entity (e.g., analytics providers, advertising networks, cloud storage providers, etc.); Business partnersGeolocationBusiness partners that receive data for their own independent use and not to provide services to a Trends International entityInferencesBusiness partners that receive data for their own independent use and not to provide services to a Trends International entity; Service providers that receive data to provide services to a Trends International entity (e.g., analytics providers, cloud storage providers, etc.); Business partners

###   

Sale or Share of Personal Information of Consumers under 16 Years of Age
------------------------------------------------------------------------

We do not knowingly sell or share (for cross-context behavioral advertising) the personal information of consumers under 16 years of age. For more information about treatment of children's personal information, see the Children's Privacy section above.

###   

What Are Your California Privacy Rights?
----------------------------------------

If you are a California resident, you can make certain requests regarding your personal information, and we will fulfill each request to the extent required by law. If we are unable to comply with your request in whole or in part, we will notify you with reasons for the denial.

As stated in more detail below, you can request that we:

1. Provide you with access to a copy of and certain details regarding the personal information we have about you.
2. Delete your personal information.
3. Stop selling your personal information or sharing your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising.
4. Correct your inaccurate personal information.
5. Limit the use or disclosure of your sensitive personal information (SPI).

To exercise any of these privacy rights, call 1-800-925-5592, press one, and say, "I'd like to exercise my privacy rights."" Or follow the instructions below specific to the type of request.

1. _Request to Access My Personal Information:_ You have the right to request access to the personal information we may have collected about you. To access your personal information, click "Request My Personal Information." Requests to access your personal information may be submitted up to two times in a rolling twelve-month period. In response, we will return to you the following categories of information, to the extent required by law:

* The categories of personal information we have collected about you.
* The categories of sources from which we collect your personal information.
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting, selling, or sharing your personal information.
* The categories of third parties to whom we disclose personal information.
* The specific pieces of personal information we have collected about you.
* A list of categories of personal information that we have sold or shared for cross-context behavioral advertising, along with the categories of third parties we sold it to or shared it with for cross-context behavioral advertising.
* A list of categories of personal information that we have disclosed for a business purpose, along with the categories of third parties we disclosed it to.

1. _Delete My Personal Information:_ You have the right to ask that we delete your personal information. Once we receive a request, we will delete the personal information (to the extent required by law) we hold about you as of the date of your request from our records and direct our service providers to do the same. Choosing to delete your personal information may impact your ability to use our websites and online features, including closure of your online account, and limit your use of in-store functions that require your personal information. To delete your personal information, click "Request My Personal Information."
2. _Stop Selling My Personal Information:_ You have the right to opt-out of the sale of your personal information or sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising and can request that we stop by clicking "My Privacy Choices" or by using the Global Privacy Control as described below.Your opt-out request may be processed differently depending on whether you are logged into your account. If you are logged in, your preference will be associated with your account, and the device on which you exercised your choice. When you log in from another device or browser, it too will be automatically opted out. If you are not logged into your account, your request will only be associated with that one browser. We also support your use of the Global Privacy Control (GPC). If you notify us of your privacy preferences through GPC, we will honor your request with respect to the browser or device that sends us the GPC signal, and when you login to your account from that device, the opt-out will extend to your account, as well. If you change your preference from opt-in to opt-out, you may be asked to confirm your preference prior to it taking effect. After opting out of the sale of your personal information or sharing of your personal information for cross-context behavioral advertising, you may still receive ads from us, however they will not be tailored to you.
3. _Correct My Personal Information:_ You have the right to ask that we correct the personal information we may have collected about you if that information is inaccurate. We reserve the right to request identifying documentation from you in certain circumstances, as permitted by law. To correct your personal information, click "Request My Personal Information."
4. _Limit the Use and Disclosure of SPI:_ You have the right to ask that we limit our use and disclosure of your SPI to certain purposes permitted by law and can do so by clicking "My Privacy Choices."

We will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights. We will not deny you goods or services, charge different prices or rates, provide a different level of service or quality of goods, or suggest that you might receive a different price or level of quality for goods. Some programs or membership services require usage of personal information to function, so compliance with your request may impact those experiences.

_How Do We Verify Your Identity to Complete Your Access, Correction and Deletion Requests:_

If you request access to, or the correction or deletion of, your personal information we will verify your identity before disclosing the requested information. To do so, we may ask that you log into your account or provide us with your:

To verify your identity, we ask you to provide your:

First name\*, Middle Initial, Last name\*

Address\*

Email address\*

Phone number

_\*Required field_

When you make a request, you will be asked to answer a few questions about yourself to help us verify your identity. Third-party identification services may help us with verification to prevent disclosure of your personal information resulting from fraudulent requests. You may be asked to log into your online account and complete a one-time passcode validation. In the event more documentation is necessary to verify your identity, we will notify you directly.

_What If You Can't Verify My Identity?_

If we can't verify your identity, we will notify you, and your request(s) to access, request, or delete your personal information may not be processed. Any requests may be denied if we have reason to believe they are fraudulent.

_How Do I Submit a Request Using an Authorized Agent_

If you'd like an authorized agent to exercise your rights for you, they may use the same links described above to submit requests. We require documentation demonstrating your agent's authority to submit requests on your behalf. For example, a valid power of attorney or other documentation, including a letter, signed by you (the California resident) authorizing the agent to submit your requests. You can download a sample letter from the request form. Documentation may be uploaded at the time you submit your request on our website or provided to us up to 10 business days after. If you submit your request by calling, you can email your forms to consumerprivacy@wal-mart.com.

_Number of Requests Received in 2022_

To view metrics about our privacy requests, click [How Many California Consumer Privacy Act Requests Did We Fulfill Last Year?](https://cpa-ui.trends%20international.com/trackrequest?brandCode=ART).

_Shine the Light_

California residents also have the right to request that we provide you with (a) a list of certain categories of personal information we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year and (b) the identity of those third parties. To exercise this right, contact us at the address provided in the How to Contact Us section below.

_Notice of Financial Incentive_

If we provide a financial incentive, we will provide you with the details, including how the incentive is related to your data before you participate so that you may make an informed decision about whether and how to participate. In the event you decide to take advantage of a financial incentive, you will always have the right to withdraw from participation and we will provide you with directions on how to do so.

###   

How we link to other websites
-----------------------------

We may provide you with links to other online services (such as social media platforms) and may include third-party features such as apps, tools, widgets, and plug ins. We may not own or control these linked online services or third-party features, and we are not responsible for the information practices of the third parties that have ownership or control over them. In some cases, these third parties operate independently from us, which means their privacy practices are not covered in this Notice. We recommend that you review their privacy statements to learn about these third parties' privacy practices, including details on the information they may collect about you.

###   

Data retention
--------------

We will keep the personal information we collect about you for as long as necessary to carry out the purposes set forth in this Privacy Notice or any other notice provided at the time of data collection, but no longer than as required or permitted under applicable law or our internal policy. We dispose of the information we collect in accordance with our retention policies and procedures.

###   

Children's privacy
------------------

Our services are intended for users ages 13 and older. We will not knowingly collect or use any personal information from persons that we know to be under the age of 13. In addition, we will delete any information in our database that we know originates from a child under the age of 13.

###   

Changes to our Privacy Notice
-----------------------------

Please check our Privacy Notice periodically for changes. We will provide additional notice of significant updates. We will post the date our Notice was last updated at the top of the Privacy Notice.

###   

How to contact us
-----------------

If you have any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of your personal information, you can contact us by clicking [here](https://www.art.com/help/talktous), sending an email to [privacy@art.com](mailto:privacy@art.com) or by contacting us at:

Art.com

5188 W. 74th Street

Indianapolis, IN 46268

World's largest selection of art

We have millions of prints, in a wide variety of styles. But more importantly, we'll help you find just the right one.

Find the perfect frame

Over 200 handcrafted frames, plus canvas, wood mount, and more. All at around 40% less than a custom frame shop.

Your walls are waiting

We can match you up with art you'll love, help create a home gallery, and even provide assistance getting it on the wall.

* * *

### 

Customer Service

### 

Business Sales

### 

About Art.com

### 

My Account

* Order Status

Keep up with the latest at Art.com.  
Sign up now & get $25 off\* your purchase of $150 or more!

Sign Up

Text GETINSPIRED to 47138.

Stay in touch with Art.com through text. Get $25 OFF $150 when you sign up.

By signing up you agree to receive recurring automated promotional and personalized marketing text messages (e.g. cart reminders) from Art.com at the cell number used when signing up. Consent is not a condition of any purchase. Reply HELP for help and STOP to cancel. Msg frequency varies. Msg & data rates may apply. View Terms at [https://attnl.tv/t/cTj/r/US](https://attnl.tv/t/cTj/r/US "https://attnl.tv/t/cTj/r/US") & Privacy at [https://attnl.tv/p/cTj](https://attnl.tv/p/cTj "https://attnl.tv/p/cTj").

\*See site terms for details, as some exclusions apply.

### 

Customer Service

### 

Business Sales

### 

About Art.com

### 

My Account

* Order Status

© Art.com All Rights Reserved.

Art.com is a registered trademark of Trends International LLC.  
Various aspects of this website are covered by issued US patent No. 7,973,796 and other pending patent applications.
